ammunitiontogo.com 2019-10-18

# Privacy Notice

**How Ammo To Go Protects Your Personally Identifiable Information**

Ammo To Go respects individual privacy and values the confidence of its customers, employees, vendors, consumers, business partners and others. Ammo To Go strives to uphold the highest ethical standards in its business practices. This Privacy Notice outlines how Ammo To Go collects, uses, and shares your Personally Identifiable Information, defined as the following:

* Name,
* Physical Address,
* Phone Number,
* Email Address,
* Credit Card.

We require the above-defined Personally Identifiable Information to be provided on all orders. From time to time, state legal rules require us to collect other information. Your Personally Identifiable Information will only be collected if you create an Ammo To Go account, or if you enter your Personally Identifiable Information into the Ammo To Go checkout process.

Ammo To Go does not sell or give away your Personally Identifiable Information to any web marketers, and you won’t see Ammo To Go ads following you around the web because we do not use your information to retarget you. Ammo To Go also does not allow third parties to collect your Personally Identifiable Information while you are on our site. The only people who we share your Personally Identifiable Information with are people who are critical to fulfilling your order: our credit card processor, our warehouse fulfillment folks, common carriers, email coordinator, and other administrative workers. You can edit the Personally Identifiable Information you provide to Ammo To Go by updating your Ammo To Go account. Subject to the above, Ammo To Go will not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to any third parties unless we receive your permission to do so or we are legally obligated to do so. Ammo To Go does not collect any information about your browsing habits on other Internet sites (with the exception of Google Analytics described below). Ammo To Go does not respond to DNT signals.

**How Ammo To Go Uses Your Non-Personal Information**

When you visit some of our web pages, Ammo To Go may collect Non-Personal Information, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Chrome), whether you are using Windows or Mac OS, the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink), and aggregate data about your visits to the Site and/or aggregate data about the pages visited. Ammo To Go uses Non-Personal Information like visitor age, gender, and shopping interests ("Aggregate Data") to improve the design and content of our site, to enable us to personalize your Internet experience, and to create services and/or products to fit your needs. Ammo To Go uses Google Analytics and Google Analytics Advertising Features, which place first and third-party cookies on your device to collect Aggregate Data. You can see how Google Analytics collects and uses Aggregate Data [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/ "here"). By using the Site, you consent to Google’s use of such Aggregate Data in the manner set forth in Google’s Terms of Service. Of course, you can always opt out of Google Analytics data collection. Just follow the process outlined on the [NAI’s opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/ "NAI’s opt-out page"), install Google’s opt-out add-on for your browser by following the process outlined [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ "here"), or adjust your settings on Google Ad Preferences.

**Nevada Opt-Out Notice**

In accordance with Nevada state law, Nevada residents may request that we never sell their Personally Identifiable Information. If you are a Nevada resident and want to submit such a request, please email [privacy@ammunitiontogo.com](mailto:privacy@ammunitiontogo.com).

**Miscellaneous**

Here are a couple more housekeeping items:

* You can make changes to your Ammo To Go account at any time. Just log in and edit your information as necessary. We appreciate you keeping your information up-to-date so we can make sure you receive your orders quickly and accurately.
* We would be happy to answer any questions you have about our privacy standards. Email us at [support@ammotogo.com](mailto:support@ammunitiontogo.com) or call us at 979-277-9676.
* Any changes to this Privacy Notice will be published on this page.
